<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Downtown Florence Unlimited</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.downtownflorenceunlimited.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.downtownflorenceunlimited.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 21:54:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.0.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Newsletter &#8211; May 2018</title>
		<link>http://www.downtownflorenceunlimited.com/2018/12/newsletter-may-2018/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 21:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.downtownflorenceunlimited.com/?p=199</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[MESSAGE FROM DFU PRESIDENT, Michelle Eubanks You&#8217;ve likely seen the article to the merger of Downtown Florence Unlimited and Main Street; it appeared in the TimesDaily in late April. The boards of&#8217; both organizations are working toward a co-created entity that will best represent the...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>MESSAGE FROM DFU PRESIDENT, Michelle Eubanks</h1>



<p>
You&#8217;ve likely seen the article to the merger of Downtown Florence Unlimited and Main Street; it appeared in the TimesDaily in late April. The boards of&#8217; both organizations are working toward a co-created entity that will best
represent the downtown, from merchants to residents, as well as maintain the pillars of national Main Street organization. It&#8217;s an exciting time, for sure! Several subcommittees related to the finances, events, and communications are meeting to help move the process forward, and we&#8217;re also crafting a new job description for the individual to be the executive director. Our goal is to have the framework for the organization established by the end of this fiscal year, which is September 30, and we&#8217;ll continue to update you &#8211; our members &#8211; along the way. Thank you for trusting us with this process and know that our downtown will be better and stronger for it!

As always, thanks for your support of Florence and its historic downtown!<br></p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<h2>DFU Committees/Information:</h2>



<h3>Membership Chair, Jeffrey Jones</h3>



<p>
&#8220;Invite new members to join us! Bring a friend! Also, if you cannot attend, please appoint someone from your business to attend for you.&#8221;<br></p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<h3>From the Parking Committee Chair, Billy Hammock:</h3>



<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><em>&#8220;<strong>PLEASE</strong>&#8211;STREET PARKING IS FOR <strong>CUSTOMERS ONLY</strong>.</em></span> Please have your employees park in garage parking.&#8221; <br></p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<h3>A message from FIRST FRIDAYS Chair, Belinda Duke:</h3>



<p>
&#8220;First Fridays theme for June is &#8220;Frontier Days&#8221; &#8211; celebrating our earliest settlers as part of our Bicentennial Celebration. Artists will demonstrate their crafts, including some of the wonderful vendors from the Pope&#8217;s Tavern Frontier Days event that will take place on June 2-3. The Jeep Club will have loads of their vehicles on static display in the center of Court Street for all to check out &#8211; the kids love this event! Also, a new addition to First Fridays will be food trucks &#8211; check them out down towards UNA past Subway! Lots of great snacks! The local Blood Mobile, help support our community &#8211; give blood. YMCA is coming to make us fit!

&#8220;The event will take place from 5-8pm on Court Street in historic downtown Florence. You can purchase your bicentennial goodies downtown as well to mark this exciting year in our grand city. Also, check out all the great downtown restaurants while you are here &#8211; we are blessed with lots of great food and great merchants in our city.

&#8220;Music will kick off on the Big River Broadcasting stage at 5pm to 8pm at Mobile Plaza and music also going on at The Gold Record Room SunTrust Bank Building.

<em>&#8220;Also, like us on face book -our UNA interns with the help of Phil Abrams our Photographer put up new information weekly highlighting the vendors -check it out!&#8221;</em></p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<h2>Upcoming Events:</h2>



<ul>
<li>May 19-20 &#8211; Arts Alive and May 18-19 Storytelling Festival</li>
<li>May 23 &#8211; Local Makers and Music Day-10-4 at the Visitor Center, McFarland Park</li>
<li>June 2 &#8211; John Coffee Cemetery Dedication Ceremony (Coffee&#8217;s Birthday)</li>
<li>June 2-3 &#8211; &#8220;Frontier Days&#8221; at Pope&#8217;s Tavern</li>
<li>June 12 &#8211; 10:30-1:30 &#8211; First Presbyterian Church &#8211; open archives and tour</li>
<li>June 23 &#8211; Korean War Veterans Meet and Greet at Pope&#8217;s Tavern</li>
</ul>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
